indiainfo.com 2017-06-26

# Dainik Bhaskar | Privacy Policy

D. B. Corp Limited is committed to protecting any personal information that you may provide to us. In particular, we believe it is important for you to know how we treat information about you that we may receive from this website.

**Information Collected**

In general, you can visit this website without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our web servers collect the domain names, not the e-mail addresses, of visitors. In addition, there are portions of this Website where we may need to collect personal information from you for a specific purpose, such as to provide you with certain information you request. The information collected from you may include your name, address, telephone, fax number, or e-mail address.

**Use of collected Information**

Domain name information that we collect is not used to personally identify you and instead is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, etc. We use this information to measure the use of our site and to improve the content of our site.

When other information is collected from you, such as your name and e-mail address, we generally let you know at the time of collection how we will use the personal information. Usually, we use the personal information you provide only to respond to your inquiry or to process your request (such as to receive newsletters). This information may be shared with other D. B. Corp Limited/ other Group businesses, but only if necessary to fulfill your request or for related purposes.

We may share the personal information you provide with other companies we have hired to provide services for us. These companies - our vendors - are contractually bound to use personal information we share with them only to perform the services we have hired them to provide. We do not share, sell, or lease personal information about you to any third-parties for their marketing use. We will release information about you if you direct us to do so, if we are required by law to do so, or in other legally limited circumstances (for example, to protect your account from fraud).

**Access to Collected Information**

You may review and update the information that you provide to us through this Website by contacting us as described below.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please use the contact Info page. We welcome your questions and suggestions about our privacy policy.

**Changes to this Policy**

Please check this privacy policy periodically to inform yourself of any changes.
